http://www.childrenofthenight.org/privacy-policy

FAQs
CHILDREN OF THE NIGHT DONOR PRIVACY POLICYChildren of the Night maintains the highest level of respect for the privacy of its donors. In furtherance of our commitment to honor your rights, the Board of Directors have developed the Donor Privacy Policy to guide our volunteers and staff on how they may and may not use your personal information.What Information We CollectChildren of the Night collects and uses various personal information from donors that includes amount donated, address, telephone number, donor comments and e-mail address. Tax laws in the United States require Children of the Night to keep contact information and contribution level of donors on file.How we use that informationChildren of the Night will never publish, sell, trade, rent or share names (unless released for publication), e-mail or mail addresses, or telephone numbers of our donors. Children of the Night will use contact information (e-mail, telephone number and address) of donors for these purposes only:Distribute receipts for donationsThank donors for their donationInform donors about upcoming fundraising and other activities of Children of the NightInternal analysis and record keepingReporting to relevant U.S. and State agencies (these reports are not for public inspection)Contact donors about changes to this policyHowever, properly anonymized donor information is not used for promotional and fundraising activities. We allow donors the option to have their name publicly associated with their donation unless the donor explicitly chooses to be “anonymous”. Financial InformationAll access to donor financial information is strictly limited to professional staff who need to process donor and financial data. No such data are given to any person, organization or group who does not need to access those data.Children of the Night only uses online payment processing services with PayPal online donation using industry standard security practices to ensure the safety of each transaction.
PayPal Privacy Policy may be viewed https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full?locale.x=en_US SSL encryption, hardware security, building security, and software security measures have all been put into practice to protect the sensitive data we collect. Children of the Night does not store, nor does it have access to your credit card information, bank account numbers, or other account data sent to those processing services.Contact UsIf you have questions about this Donor Privacy Policy or if you wish to be removed from our e-mail/postal contact lists, then please email LLee@childrenofthenight.org or write to:Children of the Night, Inc.3450 Cahuenga Blvd W, Suite 602Los Angeles, CA 90068Donor Bill of Rights –Adopted and Printed with permission of the American Association of Fund-Raising Counsel (AAFRC). April 16, 2019Philanthropy is based on voluntary action for the common good. It is a tradition of giving and sharing that is primary to the quality of life. To assure that philanthropy merits the respect and trust of the general public, and that donors and prospective donors can have full confidence in the not-for-profit organizations and causes they are asked to support, we declare that all donors have these rights:To be informed of the organization’s mission, of the way the organization intends to use donated resources, and of its capacity to use donations effectively for their intendedpurposes.To be informed of the identity of those serving on the organization’s governing board, and to expect the board to exercise prudent judgment its stewardship responsibilities.To have access to the organization’s most recent financial statements.To be assured their gifts will be used for the purposes for which they were given.To receive appropriate acknowledgment and recognition.To be assured that information about their donations is handled with respect and with confidentiality to the extent provided by law.To expect that all relationships with individuals representing organizations of interest to the donor will be professional in nature.To be informed whether those seeking donations are volunteers, employees of the organization or hired solicitors.To have the opportunity for their names to be deleted from mailing lists that an organization may intend to share.To feel free to ask questions when donating and to receive prompt, truthful and forthright answers.
